Choose some kind of bread and a
drink for tomorrow's breakfast.
Aye-aye!
Without running!
That kid doesn't listen.
Umm... for a cold, we've
got water, sports drinks...
Dairy products, and so on...
What's some food that
would be easily digested?
Rin, do you wanna get something
for tomorrow's breakfast, too?
Cereal or something?
Yeah...
Daikichi...
Did I give it to her?
Rin...
Bacteria from a cold
is all over the place.
Some people will catch it, some won't.
But you don't have to worry about
who's the one that passed it on.
Can I pick something to bring her too?
Sure.
This...
Put it in the basket.
Kouki-kun!
What are you doing in the snacks aisle?!
Kouki! What about breakfast?
It came out!
I dunno about tomorrow.
It's different than a
sacrifice. Something's off.
I don't think it's like
some penalty game.
So, why? I don't get it at all.
I'm a little bit unsatisfied,
but your presence
right now is more than just important.
There's no such thing in this world
as something never-ending.
Crying isn't painful, it's love's
sweet drops, sweet drops!
I want to keep dreaming
forever, ya know?
I want to be more kind, ya know?
As long as I’m with you, I’m happy.
Girls sure are strong, ya know?
But sometimes we're weak, ya know?
Our wish is to be happy, happy, happy!
And those days will be happy, too!
Just wanna make you happy!
My place is here!
Yeah, we're gonna go home.
I don't want your mom fussing over us.
Okay.
Here. There's food in there,
so give it to your mom.
It's heavy.
It's really heavy...
Well, let's go, Rin.
Mom! Daikichi gave us food!
Listen when somebody's talking to you!
Kouki, you don't have to...
Daikichi-san...
I'm sorry you're always
having to look after him...
O-Oh, no, I owe you for
taking care of Rin...
How is Rin-chan?
She's a lot better now.
She went back to school today. Right?
Hello...
Hello. I'm glad you're
feeling better, Rin-chan.
Yeah.
I'm making that rice gruel right now.
I'll be better soon, too.
Yep.
Rin, let's go throw my tooth!
This way!
Kouki, be careful.
Gotcha!
Nitani-san, you may have caught your
cold from Rin, taking care of her...
I'm sorry.
We're gonna throw it from here!
I meet a lot of people every day.
It's so high up...
I go to the office by train,
which is always packed.
I'm gonna throw it on that roof.
There's no way to know
who I caught it from.
So don't worry about it.
It's just a cold.
Okay.
Well, at least let me help with Kouki.
Even if it's just picking
him up from daycare...
Thank you.
Rin, we're going home.
Daikichi, let's play video games!
Sure. Next time.
Kouki, make sure to help your mom out.
Okay.
Oh, that's right.
The pudding and little
drink are from Rin.
Thank you, Rin-chan!
Pudding is my favorite!
Good night.
Daikichi, hurry up!
You're up early... It's Sunday!
I told you I'm going to practice
for the jump rope contest!
What's wrong?
This one's wobbly too...
Brush slowly.
Okay...
Don't mess with it!
Oww!
Please don't overdo it too soon.
Oh, I'm fine now.
I'm sorry to always be taking
advantage of your generosity.
I think it's the other way around.
Really, thank you.
Not at all.
I'm surprised at Kouki...
For some reason, he just can't get that.
Kouki, you're jumping too soon.
When the jump rope swings
around, you jump here, right?
Yeah.
Then you can't move your arms
and legs at the same time.
I see...
Your arms go first, then your legs.
Try it once slowly.
Got it!
Daikichi! Me too! Me too!
Okay, okay. Rin, your problem is you
swing your arms in too big circles.
Keep your arms in close like this...
Daikichi-san!
You're early, huh?!
Good morning!
Too much energy this
early in the morning...
Nobu-kun is good at it.
It's 'cause he's got a big brother.
He'll imitate everything
the older one does.
Huh...
Aren't you gonna do it, Sayaka-chan?
This time, she lost one
of her upper teeth...
Girls have it rough, even
when they're little kids...
Sayaka-chan, what kind of container
are you using to hold your teeth?
Did your parents buy you a cute one?
What's that?
You don't know about the case people use
to hold their kids' baby
teeth as a keepsake?
Keepsake?
They have these cute tiny ones.
Tiny!
Cute!
Right?
Yeah! Mine is a butterfly!
I bought one for Kouki, but...
I bet Rin would love that!
We're saving the kids' teeth, too.
I'm such an idiot! I had no
idea they had those things!
It's been like this
ever since I met Rin.
Fretting and getting nervous
over the littlest things...
Daikichi, this is for you.
I drew it at school.
Daikichi
The meat and potato stew
Daikichi makes is really
delicious. Also, Daikichi
can run very fast.
I had to write about someone at home.
Ah, well...
It's so cute!
What is this?
You put your baby teeth in
there when they come out.
It's like a keepsake...
A keepsake!
Thank you, Kouki-kun's mother!
You're welcome.
Thank you.
But isn't that Kouki's...?
It's okay, it's okay...
I throw my teeth!
...as you can see.
Until now, I've thrown all
my teeth onto the roof.
Is that okay?
That's fine, that's fine.
Throwing 'em or keeping
'em, either way works.
I see.
Rin! I'm gonna do my best with
this jump rope thing, too!
There you go, touching
your tooth again...
It'll come out on its own.
Any way you slice it, she's
gonna look like she got clocked.
As long as she doesn't smile...
There you go.
Good. Okay, let's go.
Are you getting bigger again?
Huh? You too, Daikichi-san?
I'm starting to get a spare tire...
Me too!
It's tough when you get to be our age.
Somehow, I wanna stop it in its tracks.
Daikichi-san is doing it boxer-style!
That's amazing!
It's easier on the knees this way.
Huh...
Daikichi! Teach me how to do that, too!
Forget about it!
What?! Only you get to look cool?!
First, learn how to jump
rope the normal way!
What was that?!
Get back here!
Me too! Me too!
Rin-chan, you're so good
at doing it backwards!
Wow, kids are incredible...
Really?
They have energy to burn, don't they?
Rock, paper, scissors!
I don't know where they get it from...
One more time!
Although, adults are incredible, too...
Adults?
I think you two already know
this, but I'm not Rin's dad.
We've only been living together
for about a year now.
Until then, I used all
my time for myself,
but once I started living with Rin,
my lifestyle suddenly changed...
You guys, though, you've been with
your kids ever since they were born...
For me, it's still early days,
so it's nothing, really,
but I've been wondering whether
you're okay with not having any
so-called "time for yourself"
all the way down the line...
I'm fine...
Me too!
Me too.
Really?
Well, after all...
What? What?!
Rin, come to think of it, wasn't
today the jump rope contest?
Yeah...
Rin...
I screwed up...
How many times around did you get?
15 times.
That's awful!
What about backwards-style jumping?
203 times.
You can jump like that?!
I'm gonna guess you got
first place for that?
Yeah.
Here's my certificate.
Certificate of Merit
1st year division
1st place, backwards-style jumping rope
Kaga Rin
You really did your
best. This is fantastic.
But I know I could've done better
with regular style jumping rope...
Well, they only gave you one chance...
Yeah...
Anyway, it's true that you
learned to jump rope a lot.
I know it, at least.
Right.
I lost weight!
Huh?
Cut it out!
Are we almost there?
Maybe 10 more minutes...
They'll want to see those
wobbly front teeth.
Right!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Don't touch them if you can help it!
And I'll show them how
I can jump rope, too!
Of course.
I bet my mom and dad will be surprised
to see how you've shot
up since the last time.
I wonder if I'm taller
than Auntie now.
I don't think you're that tall yet.
I'll have to tell Grandpa, too.
We're back!
Oh, Rin-chan! I've been waiting for you!
I'm home.
Look at how big you've gotten!
Are you one of the taller
kids in your class?
Yeah!
If you'd called, I would've
picked you up at the station!
Rin can walk 10 minutes!
Soon, you'll be taller than me!
Kazumi!
Yo. You're here early.
Yeah, I just got here
a little while ago.
Those clothes...
You used to wear them, right?
Yeah...
Auntie sent them to me!
Rin-chan, show me your teeth.
Okay!
Two of them in front are wobbly...
Are you okay? It doesn't hurt?
Sometimes it hurts, but I'm used to it.
I'm a pro, see?
Say, Daikichi!
Isn't there anything
you can do for her?!
Her gums are turning red!
Just a little bit...
And come to think of
it, when I was a kid,
you talked about pulling my
loose teeth out with a thread!
A thread?!
Oh, my goodness! Did I?!
I tried to make everything soft.
Thank you!
Wanna have some freeze-dried tofu?
Yeah!
I'll have boiled beans too, Auntie!
Sure!
Eat up!
I like freeze-dried tofu!
Did one come out?
Rin-chan?
It came out!
Blood! Blood!
Mom! Tissue! Tissue!
Hold on! Hold on!
I'm fine!
Rin, use this for now!
That's a dust cloth!
Rin-chan has changed a lot.
I don't know...
This might just be the real Rin...
Huh...
So, you're getting married?
Mom was saying...
Yeah.
Good for you. She said he
seemed like a nice guy.
Yeah, well...
The only thing I'm not on board with
is he wants to have a kid right away.
That's a good thing, isn't it?
Are you kidding me?!
I wouldn't be able to go out
drinking or go to concerts
or go on trips or eat delicious food...
I wouldn't be able to
do anything anymore!
Well, you gotta talk to
your husband about that.
I wouldn't know...
I'm not into kids in the first place!
And I don't wanna become one
of those pushy moms either!
I'm not confident that I could
sacrifice myself to raise a kid...
Ah, I think you'd manage somehow.
If you put your mind to it...
Sometimes you just have to manage...
Easy for you to say, big brother...
Yeah, maybe...
What's that?
I've never become a father or
husband, let alone a mother.
It's burning...
Yeah.
True, I don't have time
to shop at my leisure,
or chat with friends over coffee...
But my time at work is my own time...
And my time with my
son is also my time...
Precious time...
Other parents might look like it,
but I don't think they're
doing anything special.
If you look around you, you'll see
mothers and fathers galore like that.
I see...
Right...
Grandpa, you know what?
Some of my adult teeth are coming in.
Hey! Rin!
Th-This is sweat!
Daikichi!
Hurry up!
Say "cheese"!
Tasu Elementary School Entrance Ceremony
That jar...
Masako-san had it, too...
I'll be right back!
Daikichi!
What?! The other one's coming loose?!
Mirror! Mirror!
I bet I'll still keep getting
nervous and worked up
over minor stuff from here on out.
I suppose it's the same
way with those two...
Does it hurt?
Rin!
Daikichi, look at this!
What the heck? It's like
you've got a cat's face!
I know, right?
Send a text to your parents' house!
You mean a photo?
Even so, it seems like that smile
will be my happiness from now on...
Yeah!
Hurry up!
Okay, open your mouth.
And I guess I don't think there's
anything wrong with that.
A sunny early Sunday afternoon
Let's go somewhere today
It's the same road I'm used to traveling
But I can see it sparkling so bright
With the sun shining down its warmth
And you here by my side...
I'm already high, high, high
I feel like dashing out
Sing, la, la, la
My voice out to forever
I'm already high, high, high
Ride the dancing wind
Sing, la, la, la
My voice springs up
Daikichi!!